britannia.com 2003-12-02

# Britannia Privacy Statement

**Britannia Privacy Statement**  

Britannia, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

**Consumer Information**   
During the process of delivering content and advertising to you, Britannia does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, if you voluntarily register as a Britannia member, register for our email newsletter/bulletin, or enter our sweepstakes, you knowingly provide us with your email address, name, age, residence, hobbies, surfing habits, etc. This information will not be sold to list brokers or used for any purpose other than to deliver to you information you have requested or information pertaining to interests you may have indicated.

Our statistical programs track traffic and in the process obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider used to connect to the Internet, browser type, or the type of computer operating system used (Macintosh or Windows, for example), country resided in, how long connected to the site, pages accessed, etc.

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, an ad service may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by advertisers to respond to your request. In addition, ad services may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website. 

**Data Collection and Cookies**   
Britannia, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. We cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time you register as a Britannia member. This unique number is then stored in a cookie file on your computer, and it tells us not to display the registration form when you return to Britannia or click to another page on the site. At this time we do not use cookies for any other purpose.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

Copyright ©2001 Britannia.com, LLC
